I was told that you can have up to eight pieces without any restrictions.
Should we get?
Yes?
- The worst thing is that you are serious too.
I know you!
- Yes Yes.
Certainly.
I see how our garden can be open and drooling and getting rid of all the tall grass and ...
It can be very nice of the alpacas.
It smokes over there.
It is the hot tub that we will swim in later.
They keep on warming it.
It takes three hours.
- Oh, what a cute!
- Very nice.
- Oh, wow!
- (Harry) What is this?
Oh, Alma ... you found directly on the sofa.
- It's hard to miss with these pillows.
- Alpacka pillows!
Oh my God!
Got you!
(I got you there!)
- What are you doing, Alma?
- I look in the menu.
Well, it's a small hole here so Alma looked through it.
You can spy on people.
How fun.
So, check out these breads.
Here is our starter.
A little "Skagen-Alpacka-Toast" and mozzarella salad.
- (Alma) Harry, could I get Bregott?
- Absolutely.
You do not understand the good of life that has bregott on the sandwich.
How does it feel, Joanna?
It is fantastic!
We had to go in ourselves here in the morning and feed them.
It's such an experience!
I just stand and smile.
You will be happy with them!